ALISON HURT

4524 Circle Ave, Cincinnati, OH 45232 alisonrhurt@gmail.com (859)983-6036 linkedin.com/in/alisonrhurt

Software Developer with 5+ years experience in database management, financial program coordination, and client relations. As a Salesforce Administrator, I created and implemented technical internal trainings and translated data into user friendly reports.

Excited to use my analytical and problem solving skills in a team oriented full stack development role.

TECHNICAL & SOFT SKILLS

Object Oriented Programming: C#, .NET

Web Application Development: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Servlets, JSP, Spring Web MVC

Database Programming: JDBC, table design/creation, SQL queries and DML, PostgreSQL

Development tools: Agile, unit testing (JUnit), integration testing, Git, unix command line navigation

Other Technologies: Adobe Design Suite, Microsoft Suite

Soft Skills: Internal & external communications, public speaking, project management, teamwork minded & detail oriented

EDUCATION

Tech Elevator - Cincinnati, OH May - September 2018

Full Stack .Net Certification

Programming immersion program focusing on developing dynamic web based software systems using .Net

Northern Kentucky University

June 2009

Bachelor of Arts in Design

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Cincinnati WorksAug 2015 - May 2018Brighton CenterJuly 2013 - Aug 2015

Financial Services Coordinator

- LISC Salesforce administration- built comprehensive reports resulting in a 25% increase of yearly FOC grants
- Created and implemented internal Salesforce process trainings which lead to more cohesive team outcomes
- Managed the financial services department and spearheaded continuous improvements to financial literature and contracts
- Coordinated Tax Preparation events resulting in several new business partnerships and 50+ new customer relationships in 2018
- Selected for the **WCPO "Next Nine" award** in February 2018, the 'Employee of the Year' award in January 2018, and the 'Quarterly Employee Award' in March 2017

Oh! Darling Vintage

Owner/Operations Manager

January 2010 - January 2014

- Responsible for all product development, financial and tax management, marketing and client relations
- · Coordinated staffing, managed purchasing and inventory, and handled all accounting and billing activity

Evenflo

Design Internship June 2009 - December 2010

- Contributed to car seat fabric design, market research, trend forecasting and fabric sourcing
- Created a fabric organizational system for hundreds of current Evenflo fabrics which decreased item search time by 75%